maxabout.com 2018-06-04

# Privacy Policy

MaxAbout.com takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

## What This Privacy Policy Covers

This policy covers how MaxAbout.com treats personal information that MaxAbout.com collects and receives, including information related to your past use of MaxAbout.com products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that MaxAbout.com does not own or control, or to people that MaxAbout.com does not employ or manage.

##  Information Collection and Use

**General**  
MaxAbout.com collects personal information when you register with MaxAbout.com, when you use MaxAbout.com products or services, when you visit MaxAbout.com pages or the pages of certain MaxAbout.com partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. MaxAbout.com may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 

When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. For some financial products and services we may also ask for your address, Social Security number, and information about your assets. Once you register with MaxAbout.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 

MaxAbout.com collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of financial products and services that we offer. 

MaxAbout.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, MaxAbout.com cookie information, and the page you request. 

MaxAbout.com uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

**Information Collected About You**

We may collect “Non-Personal Information” – information that cannot be used to identify you – via Cookies, even if you have not registered with or provided any Personal Information to Publisher Name. 

**What Choices Do I Have?**

Most browser software can be set to reject Cookies, and you can opt out of Cookies for several Ad Servers by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative gateway opt-out site. 

**How Information Collected About You Is Used?**

Third parties may use Non-Personal Information in order to display advertising that reflects the interests and preferences of our user community.

**Use of Site Browsing History**

By using Maxabout.com you consent to collection, storage, and use of your browsing history on this website. We share this information with trusted 3rd parties that use it to show you marketing communications of interest only. While no Personally Identifiable Information is shared, we respect your right to privacy hence this transparent disclosure. In addition, we respect your right to opt out. If you want to opt out from this program, please click on the link below and select the appropriate option on the destination page – [Opt Out Page](http://www.adobe.com/in/privacy/opt-out.html?button=Opt-Out). In addition, most setup your browser software to reject 3rd party cookies. In addition, you can opt out of several similar programs by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) gateway opt-out site.

**Children**

When a child under age 13 attempts to register with MaxAbout.com, we ask that he or she have a parent or guardian create a MaxAbout.com Family Account to obtain parental permission. 

MaxAbout.com will not contact children under age 13 about special offers or for marketing purposes without a parent's permission. 

MaxAbout.com does not ask a child under age 13 for more personal information, as a condition of participation, than is reasonably necessary to participate in a given activity or promotion. 

##  Information Sharing and Disclosure

MaxAbout.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with MaxAbout.com under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help MaxAbout.com communicate with you about offers from MaxAbout.com and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 

We have a parent's permission to share the information if the user is a child under age 13. Parents have the option of allowing MaxAbout.com to collect and use their child's information without consenting to MaxAbout.com sharing of this information with people and companies who may use this information for their own purposes; 

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of MaxAbout.com's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

We transfer information about you if MaxAbout.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, MaxAbout.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

MaxAbout.com displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area. 

MaxAbout.com does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. 

MaxAbout.com advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies). 

MaxAbout.com works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business. For more information regarding providers of products or services that you've requested please read our detailed reference links. 

##  Cookies

MaxAbout.com may set and access MaxAbout.com cookies on your computer. MaxAbout.com lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to MaxAbout.com's cookies. 

MaxAbout.com uses web beacons to access MaxAbout.com cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with MaxAbout.com products and services. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.

##  Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences

**General**  
We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the MaxAbout.com service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the MaxAbout.com Newsletter, that are considered part of your MaxAbout.com account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. 

You can delete your MaxAbout.com account by visiting our Account Deletion page. Please click here to read about information that might possibly remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted. 

**Children**

Parents can review, edit, and delete information relating to their child's MaxAbout.com account using tools offered by MaxAbout.com Family Accounts.

If a parent chooses not to allow us to further collect or use a child's information, parents enrolled in MaxAbout.com Family Accounts can delete their child's account by signing into that child's account and then visiting our Account Deletion page. Please click here to read about information that might possibly remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted. 

##  Confidentiality and Security 

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 

##  Changes to this Privacy Policy

MaxAbout.com may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your MaxAbout.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

##  Questions and Suggestions 

If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#55363a3b2134362120261538342d34373a20217b363a38).
